import 'Catalog/en/foreign-languages/greek/greek.css';


// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/gb.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: [],


}



export var cards = {
  "Alpha": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Α</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Alpha"
  },
  "Beta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Β</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Beta"
  },
  "Gamma": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Γ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Gamma"
  },
  "Delta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Δ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Delta"
  },
  "Epsilon": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Ε</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Epsilon"
  },
  "Zeta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Ζ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Zeta"
  },
  "Eta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Η</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Eta"
  },
  "Theta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Θ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Theta"
  },
  "Iota": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Ι</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Iota"
  },
  "Kappa": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Κ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Kappa"
  },
  "Lambda": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Λ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Lambda"
  },
  "Mu": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Μ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Mu"
  },
  "Nu": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Ν</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Nu"
  },
  "Xi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Ξ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Xi"
  },
  "Omicron": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Ο</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Omicron"
  },
  "Pi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Π</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Pi"
  },
  "Rho": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Ρ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Rho"
  },
  "Sigma": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Σ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Sigma"
  },
  "Tau": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Τ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Tau"
  },
  "Upsilon": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Υ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Upsilon"
  },
  "Phi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Φ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Phi"
  },
  "Chi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Χ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Chi"
  },
  "Psi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Ψ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Psi"
  },
  "Omega": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>Ω</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "Omega"
  }
  
};